<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">myAlly</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="default_text">--</string>
    <string name="subj_measure">How are you feeling right now?</string>
    <string name="obj_instruction">Let\'s measure your heart rate now! Please put your finger on the camera lens</string>
    <string name="angry">Angry</string>

    <string name="hr_desc">Your current heart rate:</string>
    
    <!-- Temporary String -->
    <string name="quote">\"Our greatest glory consists not in never failing, but in rising every time we fall.\" - Oliver Goldsmith</string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="cd_crisis">Crisis</string>
    <string name="cd_homework">Homework</string>
    <string name="cd_community">Community</string>
    <string name="cd_balloon">Breathing Balloon</string>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>\"Our greatest glory consists not in never failing, but in rising every time we fall.\" - Oliver Goldsmith</item>
        <item>\"The best and most beautiful things in the world cannot be seen or even touched - they must be felt with the heart.\" - Helen Keller</item>
        <item>\"It is during our darkest moments that we must focus to see the light.\" - Aristotle</item>
        <item>\"Find a place inside where there\'s joy, and the joy will burn out the pain.\" - Joseph Campbell</item>
        <item>\"Don\'t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.\" - Robert Louis Stevenson</item>
        <item>\"Nothing is impossible, the word itself says \'I\'m possible\'!\" - Audrey Hepburn</item>
        <item>\"Happiness is not something you postpone for the future; it is something you design for the present.\" - Jim Rohn</item>
        <item>\"Happiness resides not in possessions, and not in gold, happiness dwells in the soul.\" - Democritus</item>
        <item>\"Thousands of candles can be lighted from a single candle, and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases by being shared.\" - Buddha</item>
        <item>\"Your present circumstances don\'t determine where you go; they merely determine where you start.\" - Nido Qubein</item>
        <item>\"Change your thoughts and you change your world.\" - Norman Vincent Peale</item>
        <item>\"We can\'t help everyone, but everyone can help someone.\" - Ronald Reagan</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>